<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Two Activites Challenge</string>
    <string name="btn_text_one">Text One</string>
    <string name="btn_text_two">Text Two</string>
    <string name="btn_text_three">Text Three</string>
    <string name="activity2_name">Second Activity</string>
    <string name="button_1_heading">FRIENDSHIP</string>
    <string name="button_1_content">
        Friendship is the most significant just as valuable endowments of life. Friendship is one of the most esteemed relationships. Individuals who have old buddies appreciate the most in their life. Genuine friendship depends on faithfulness and support. An old buddy is a person who will remain with you when challenges are out of control.
        \n\n
        A friend is somebody unique on whom you can depend on to praise every second. Friendship resembles an actual asset, and it can lead us to progress. Everything relies upon our decision on how we pick our friends. Selecting a real friend in your life can be a task. If you choose a bad companion, they can mislead you, but real friends will always guide you the right way.
        \n\n
        The nature of friendship is necessary for our satisfaction. The advantages of true friendship stay long-life. Likewise, having a reliable friend circle additionally improves our fearlessness. True friendship can’t be worked inside constrained limits like position or statement of faith. It gives us an inclination that somebody needs us, and we are not the only ones. This is genuine that a person can’t live alone.
        \n\n
        Generally, we make a companion with people who are of a similar age as our own. The same age gathering can allow you to share anything. Friendship is a connection that can make or break us in each phase of life. However, friendship is a precious advantage. It is likewise not all that simple to look after friendships. It requests your time just as endeavors. Last but not least, it is elusive and genuine friendship; however, once you prevail in this relationship, you will make some brilliant memories. In return for that, a companion will need your significant time and trust.
        \n\n
        Resource: https://www.aplustopper.com/paragraph-on-friendship/</string>

    <string name="button_2_heading">LOVE</string>
    <string name="button_2_content">
        Having mutual love is significant for keeping up with any relationship for quite a while. Genuine love is always extremely valuable and selfless. The person who loves you will acknowledge you with no conditions and won’t expect you to be perfect. He/she will consistently attempt to keep you happy with all the methods he/she can.
        \n\n
        Parent and child relationship is the most grounded and remarkable case of love. They love their kid since birth to the world, and nothing can better likely express what caring affection it is. Also, the kid adores his parents similarly and has a sense of safety each time in their presence.
        \n\n
        Love for our grandparents and other older relative is remarkably helpful. Those are the ones who had helped us in learning new things in our adolescence. We can make them feel honored distinctly by rewarding them with love and care. They will consistently be with us in our troublesome times.
        \n\n
        Our siblings assume a critical job in molding our life. The elder one of our siblings consistently manages us with affection, and we ought to consistently be obedient to them. Our young sibling needs our adoration and cares for separating among good and bad. Our love esteems much for them.
        \n\n
        Everybody makes a few companions at various phases of life. A few companionships last more while some end in only a couple of months. The fundamental explanation for it is the presence of love. Indeed, even we ought to have a sentiment of affection for the needy and poor. They deserve our love the most. We should that is why show our love and affection to everybody irrespective of any differences among each other.
        \n\n
        Resource: https://www.aplustopper.com/paragraph-on-love/#:~:text=Paragraph%20On%20Love%3A%20The%20main,a%20strong%20feeling%20for%20everybody.
    </string>

    <string name="button_3_heading">SELF CONFIDENCE</string>
    <string name="button_3_content">
        Self Confidence is the key to success, or we can say the first step to success. If a person has self confidence, he has won half the battle. Those people who have self confidence at work, school, and in their daily life always appear on top of world. Everything seems to go right for these people and they always seem to present themselves as calm, collected and successful in everything they do.
        \n\n
        If you pay attention, you might notice that these self confident people usually are successful in every area of their lives. Is this because they are smarter? Or is it because they have more money? Maybe they are just lucky? The reality is that none of these things are true. Self confident people understand the impact of believing in themselves and relying on their abilities.
        \n\n
        This confidence ultimately creates opportunities for success and with each new success, another self confidence building block is put into place. Success builds self confidence with each new achievement. Self confident people perceive themselves as able to achieve those things they set out to do and this perception creates reality in their lives.
        \n\n
        Yes, perception creates reality. You can become the person you want to be. You have heard it said that if you can believe it you can achieve it.
        \n\n
        So, start believing in yourself, act on that belief, and you ill start building self confidence in your life. Building self confidence need certain steps to be followed.
        \n\n
        Make a list of your strong points. Note down all the positive things about yourself and the things that you are good at doing. Think of compliments you have received or things that come easily to you. It doesn’t matter what it is, if it’s good, write it down.
        \n\n
        Choose two of those things that you want to improve in yourself. It’s important to succeed and by concentrating on the areas you are already good at you will have a better chance of becoming even surer of yourself. Remember that success builds upon success.
        \n\n
        Exude confidence even if you don’t feel like it. Talk to yourself in an encouraging way and stay away from negative thoughts and people as you can. Surround yourself with positive, confident, and successful people. This will become a habit and will build confidence.
        \n\n
        Look at yourself in a different way than you are used to doing. It can change your life and help your confidence level to rise.
        \n\n
        Resource: https://www.shareyouressays.com/essays/short-speech-on-self-confidence-507-words/2831
    </string>

</resources>